&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：以这些为基础，这些抽象操作作为
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: With those as our foundation, those abstract operations as
我们的基础现在是我们换档和真正的强制话题的时候了。
our foundation it is now time for us to switch gears and really topic of coercion.
顺便说一句，正如我在片场所说的，这将需要
And by the way as I said at the out set, this is going to require for
如果你能从我接下来要说的话中得到任何东西，它将会
you to get anything out of what I'm about to say over this next bit it's gonna
要求你有一个开放的心态。
require you to have an open mind.
因为你天生就相信这是一辆邪恶的马车
Because you have been so programmed to believe that this is an evil buggy
JavaScript中应该避免的可怕部分，
horrible part of JavaScript that you should avoid,
很难从这个讨论中看到任何价值或价值。
that it's hard to see any value or merit out of this discussion.
但我把它放在这门课程的顶端
But I make it such a point of put it in the very top of this course
因为我认为这是最被低估的
because I think it's one of the most under valued and
下面看一下所有JavaScript中的东西。
under looked that things in all of JavaScript.
所以首先，我知道你们大多数人都遵循这种行为
So to start off with I know most of you follow that behavior and
那条建议说，不，我只是避免强迫。
that advice that says, no I just avoid coercions.
我只是使用三重等于，我不处理类型，也不是很多。
I just use the triple equals, I don't deal with types, not so much.
让我们看看一些示例，在这些示例中，您已经在进行强制
Let's look at some examples where you're already doing coercion
不管你有没有意识到。
whether you realize it or not.
有没有人在几年前使用ES6，模板文字字符串？
Any of you use the ES6 as of a few years ago, the template-literal strings?
是啊。我肯定到处都在用这些。
Yeah. I certainly use these all over the place.
这是一个缓慢的烧伤。
This is one of those slow burns.
因为当它第一次出现的时候，我并不是真的关心这个功能，而且
Cuz when it first came out, I didn't really care about this feature, and
现在我喜欢这个功能。
now I love this feature.
可能是我最喜欢的三个功能。
Might be on my top three favorite features.
我一直在使用它，特别是在我的colsole.log语句中。
I use it all the time, especially in my colsole.log statements.
我只是到处使用它，我喜欢模板字符串。
I just use it everywhere and I love template strings.
如果您将值放入这些表达式中，
And if you drop in values into those expressions,
可能，就像你们所有人一样，那些已经不是弦的东西。
that aren't already strings, probably, like all of you.
猜猜那里发生了什么？
Guess, what's happening there?
这个数字让Coers变成了一个字符串，隐含的，邪恶的，
That number is getting coers to a string, implicitly, evil,
你们已经在强迫了，你们所有人，就是这样。
you're already doing coercion, all of you, period.
不管道格·克劳福德说什么你都在强迫
No matter what Doug Crawford said, you're doing coercion,
你在你的程序中依赖强制。
you're relying upon coercion in your programs.
这不是一件坏事，这是一件非常棒的事情。
And that's not a bad thing, that's a perfectly great thing.
但在掩护之下，你应该有一个心智模型，知道发生了什么
But under the covers, you should have the mental model that what's happening
这是我取一个字符串，msg1，并把它加到一个数字上。
here is I'm taking a string, msg1, and adding it to a number.
&GT；&GT；Kyle Simpson：现在，为什么最终会产生一种胁迫？
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Now, why is that end up producing a coercion?
嗯，它实际上调用了另一个小魔术
Well, it's actually invoking another a little magical
程序员喜欢做的事情就是我们有运算符重载。
thing that programmers love to do which is we've got operator overloading.
加运算符通常被认为是在做数值运算。
The plus operator is normally thought of is doing numerical operation.
想什么？
Thought?
规范说，如果您将加号运算符与字符串一起使用，
The spec says that if you use the plus operator with something that's a string,
这里有一个你们很多人可能都做过的例子。
and here's an example that lot of you have probably done.
向事物添加空字符串以将其转换为数字。
Add an empty string to a thing to turn it into a number.
你有没有停下来想过这是怎么回事？
Did you ever stop to wonder how that worked?
这是因为说明书上说加号运算符。
Well, it's because the specs says that the plus operator.
如果它们中的任何一个是字符串，请注意或那里，如果它们中的任何一个是
If either one of them is a string, notice that or there, if either one of them is
字符串时，加号运算符更喜欢字符串连接。
a string, the plus operator prefers string concatenation.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：这意味着，如果其中只有一个是字符串，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Which means, if only one of them is a string,
猜猜另一个会发生什么？
guess what's gonna happen to the other one?
两个字符串的操作就在那里，在7.A。
A two-string operation right there on 7.a.
它将对其调用两个字符串的抽象操作，并且
It's gonna call a two string abstract operation on it, and
把它变成一个字符串，里面有所有的怪异之处。
turn it in to a string with all of the weirdnesses in caveats there of.
当它是一个格式良好的数字时，比如数字16，没什么大不了的。
When it's a well formed number, like the number 16, not such a big deal.
但是在数字上有很多拐角处的情况，而且
But there's lots of corner cases on numbers, and
很多关于其他值的转角情况，你只是愉快地调用这些东西，
lots of corner cases on other values, and you're just invoking these things happily,
一点也不担心你在使用强制手段。
and not worrying at all, about the fact that you're using coercion.
不，我不是来告诉你停止使用胁迫的，我是来告诉你
No, I'm not here to tell you to stop using coercion, I'm here to tell you
你在使用强制，所以学习它对你来说不是有意义的吗？
you're using coercion, so wouldn't it make sense for you to learn it?
这就是为什么我们潜入这个领域，好吗？
That's why we dive into this, okay?
所以，你可能会说，好吧，听着，我不喜欢做那些隐含的强迫，
So, you may say, well, listen, I don't like to do those implicit coercions,
我想把这件事说得非常明确。
I wanna be super explicit about it.
好的，所以，这里有一些疯狂的方法你可以直截了当地说出来，
Okay, so, here's some crazy ways that you can be explicit about it,
我前几天才学到这个。
I just learned this one the other day.
我从来没有想过你可以把一个值放入一个数组中，
I never even considered that you could throw a value into an array,
只将一个值放入数组中，然后对其调用点连接。
just the one value into an array, and then call dot join on it.
这实际上是字符串it，即使它没有字符串连接
And that actually ends up string it even though it does no string concatenation at
总之，该联接的规范首先将其转换为字符串。
all, the spec for that join first turns it into a string.
不要这样做这是个糟糕的主意，但如果你想超级直白的话你可以的
Don't do this that's a terrible idea, but you could if you wanna be super explicit
关于，你可以说，听着，我只是在这里做字符串连接。
about, you could say listen, I'm only doing string concatenations here.
所以我要明确地把我的号码变成一个字符串。
So I'm gonna be explicit about turning my number into a string.
这里有一些其他的可能格式更好一些。
Here's some other ones that are maybe a little more well formed.
例如，您可以调用toString方法。
You might, for example, call the toString method.
好的，酷，至少标签上的toString方法说明了它在做什么。
Okay, cool, the toString method at least on the label says what it's doing.
它会把一个数字变成一个字符串，这样就不会太糟糕了。
It's gonna turn a number into a string so that's not too bad.
这里有一个小奇怪的地方，就是你是如何调用一个方法的
There's a little weirdness here which is how are you calling a method on
原始值？
a primitive value?
原始值没有方法。
Primitive values don't have methods.
所以你实际上已经在这里做隐式强制
So you're actually already still doing implicit coercion here and
我们稍后再谈这一点。
we'll come back to that.
如果你根本不想做任何隐含的强迫，
If you don't wanna do any implicit coercion at all,
基本上你唯一的选择。
basically your only option.
是在没有新关键字符串情况下使用基本对象，
Is to use that fundamental object without a new keyword string,
这是我喜欢的将数字明确强制为字符串的方法，
and this is my preferred way of explicitly coercing that number to a string,
大写的S字符串函数将为您实现这一点。
the capital S string function is gonna do that for you.
所以，如果你是那些说嘿，听着，所有这些隐含的事情的人之一，
So, if you're one of those that says hey, listen, all those implicit things,
这些都很神奇，我们不想做，而且
those are magical and we don't wanna do them, and
你想要明确，有一个明确的例子。
you wanna be explicit about it, there's an example of being explicit about it.
我不确定这是个好主意
I'm not so sure that that's a great idea
在所有情况下，但这至少是一种明确的方式。
in all cases, but that's at least a way of being explicit.
好的，所以字符串到，数字到字符串好的，但是
All right, all right, all right, so string to, number to string all right, but
反过来呢？
what about the other way around?
[笑]你已经在这么做了。
[LAUGH] You're already doing that too.
因为你们所有人都在处理Web应用程序，或者
Because all of you are dealing with web applications, or
至少你们大多数人都在处理Web应用程序，这意味着
at least most of you are dealing with web applications which means
您正在处理来自表单元素之类的用户输入。
you're dealing with user input from things like form elements.
这意味着你把东西当做字符串来抓，而且
Which means you're grabbing things as strings, and
然后你只是和他们一起做数值的事情。
then you're just doing numeric stuff with them.
当你在加号运算中抛出字符串值时，就像我在这里做的那样，
When you throw that string value at the plus operation, like I'm doing here,
猜猜会发生什么？
guess what happens?
哦，我们得到了一个字符串连接。
Oops, we get a string concatenation.
我们得到的不是17，而是字符串161。
Instead of getting 17, we get the string 161.
但是好的，我会继续强迫它成为一个数字。
But okay, okay, I'll go ahead and force it to be a number.
好的，有两种方法迫使它成为1号，这里的加号运算符。
Okay, there's two ways of forcing it to be a number one, this plus operator here.
一元加号运算符，如果您在规范中查找它的话。
The unary plus operator, if you'll look in the spec for it.
猜猜它调用了什么抽象操作，当我们预期结果是这样的时候
Guess what it invokes which abstract operation when we expect that turns out
两个数字的抽象运算，好吗？
that the two number abstract operation, okay?
只是确保你一直都在，好吗？
Just making sure you're all the way, okay?
它调用两个数字运算，就是这样。
It invokes the two number operation, that's all it does.
所以我们在这里说，拿着这个东西，那是一根绳子或者其他什么东西，然后
So here we're saying take that thing that's a string or whatever it is, and
在我们把它传进去之前把它变成一个数字。
turn it into a number before we pass it in.
如果它是字符串形式的格式良好的数值表示形式，则对于
If it's a well-formed numeric representation in string form, for
例如，你会在这里得到很好的结果，比如17。
example, you're gonna end up with good results here, like 17.
如果它是空的，猜猜你最后会得到什么？
If it's empty, guess what you're gonna end up with?
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：空字符串会变成什么？
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: What's the empty string gonna become?
零，这可能不是你想要的，但它会发生的。
Zero, it may not be what you want but it's gonna happen.
所以这里有另一个例子，这种强迫到处都在发生。
So here's another example this kind of coercion happens all over the place.
我最大的挫败感是人们不处理它，然后只是有点
And my biggest frustration is that people don't deal with it and then just sort of
这就是我不需要担心类型和胁迫的全部。
slap a name badge on this is all I don't have to worry about types and coercion.
我很好，就是这个，这就是虫子的来源。
I'm good it's this, this is where bugs come from.
使用你不知道它们是如何工作的工具。
Using tools that you don't understand how they work.
好的，让我更具体地说，即使是在加号运算符中，
Okay, so let me be more specific about it, even in the plus operator,
因为它可能看起来有点奇怪。
cuz it might look a little weird.
你可以使用基本数函数，好的。
You can use the fundamental number function, okay.
这是我喜欢的方式。
This is my preferred way.
如果我要将某物转换为数字，我使用Number函数。
If I'm gonna turn something into a number, I use the number function.
我们没有两个数字，所以这基本上是最具语义的方式
We don't have a two number, so this is basically the most semantic way of telling
代码的阅读器，你要用一些东西做一个数字。
the reader of code that you're gonna make a number out of something.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：例如，如果使用负运算符，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: If you use a minus operator for example,
如果你们谁对我太挖苦，我就踢你们。
if any of you get too sarcastic with me I'm gonna kick you up.
如果您使用减运算符，则只为数字定义了减号。
If you use the minus operator that one is only defined for numbers.
它没有超载
That it's not overloaded for
字符串，从一个字符串中减去另一个字符串没有任何意义。
string, it wouldn't make any sense to subtract one string from another.
所以上面的负运算符，会做什么？
So that minus operator up there, is gonna do what?
凯尔·辛普森：来吧？
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Come on?
两个数字，好吗？
Two number, okay?
它将调用两个数字抽象操作。
It's gonna invoke that two number abstract operation.
这些都是在你的程序中以各种不同的方式发生的事情。
These are all things that are happening in your programs in various different ways.
我认为我们把这些事情说出来会是个好主意
And I think it would be a good idea for us to call these things out and
要更多地意识到有意隐姓埋名。
be a lot more aware of incognito of it intentionally about.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：好的，字符串和数字总是工作的东西，但你
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Okay, okay, okay, strings and numbers are always work things but you
知道我从来没有做过什么，因为我从来没有在强迫我的布尔值上乱搞，对吧？
know what I never do, because I never mess around with coercion my Boolean, right?
因为我从来不写在if类中使用非布尔值的if语句。
Cuz I never write if statements that use non-Booleans in the if class.
你们中的任何人都使用LIKE检查来查看字符串是否是非空的
Any of you use like checking to see if a string is non-empty
看它是不是真的？
to see whether it's truthy or not?
非常普遍的做法，猜猜这叫什么强制。
Extremely common practice, guess what that's called coercion.
好的，你猜怎么着？
Okay, and guess what?
所有怪异的强制布尔式角落案例都是事实，
All of the weird corner cases of coercion Booleans are in a fact,
即使用你的简单的if语句，它们也是事实。
even with your little simple if statements they're in a fact.
事实上，我会说布尔值有更多的角落情况，
Matter of fact, I would say there are more corner cases with boolean,
也许比其他任何类型的总理都要好
maybe than any other premier of type or
在我们走的时候，我们将进入这里的各种疲劳，所以空线，
kinds of wearnesses that we're gonna get into here as we go So that empty string,
如果学生输入的值是空的，那就是假的，对吗？
if students input that value as an empty that's gonna be falsy, alright?
但是如果字符串中只有一串空白呢？
But what if that string has just a bunch of white space in it?
现在它会是真实的，对吗？
Now it's gonna be truthy, right?
这不是您关心的有效字符串，因为
It's not a valid string that you care about because
它有一堆空白，但突然之间，它将是真实的。
it's got a bunch of white space in it but all of a sudden it's going to be truthy.
即使用我们的布尔值。
Corner cases even with our Boolean.
另一个最喜欢的是，人们喜欢使用数字的强制
Another favorite one, people love to use the numeric coercion of a number
或者零或者非零代表真或假，对吗？
to either a zero or a non zero for truthy or falsy, right?
所以如果我的长度是零，那么它就变成了假的
So if my length is zero then it becomes false and
如果我的长度是任何非零，那么它就成真了。
if my length is anything non zero then it becomes true.
因为它不是零中的一个，将不得不依赖于这一点。
Because it's not one of the zeros, will have to rely up on that.
除了当它是南的时候会发生什么。
Except what happens when it's NaN.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：好的，在所有这些胁迫中都有各种各样的角落案例。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Okay, there's all kinds of corner cases in all of these coercions.
所以如果你有使用这些东西的习惯
So if you're in the habit of using some of these and
不使用别人，我的意思是我讨厌这样说，但它有点虚伪
not using others, I mean I hate to call this out but it sort of hypocritical
也就是说，我使用了这种形式或魔法，但我不喜欢那种形式的魔法。
to say, I used this form or magic but I don't like that form of magic.
我不知道我们是否应该使用魔法，
I don't know if we should use the magic at all,
我认为我们应该学习它，使用它，然后它就一点也不神奇了。
I think we should learn it, use it, and then it's not magical at all.
一旦你学会了，你就是故意的，
Once you learn it, you're doing something intentional,
你在向其他人传达你的意图。
and you're communicating your intent to other people.
这并不意味着含蓄总是不好的。
That does not mean that implicitness is always bad.
事实上，含蓄是非常有用的。
As a matter of fact, implicitness can be very useful.
它只是意味着我们必须非常小心和有意。
It just simply means we have to be very careful and intentional.
所以你可能会说，好吧，我喜欢把我的全部变成显式布尔值。
So you might say well I like to turn all of mine into explicit booleans.
所以你可能会用到这一点。
So you might use that.
在一号线上双重否定。
Double negate up there on line one.
这告诉它，成为一个布尔值。
Tha's telling it, become a boolean.
我在这张幻灯片上没有，但是
I don't have it on this slide, but
您还可以使用基本大写B布尔值。
you could also use the fundamental capital B Boolean.
这就是我喜欢做的。
That's what I prefer to do.
就像错开一个数字一样，我更喜欢使用大写的B布尔值。
Just like straying a number, I prefer to use capital B Boolean.
但是对于数字，它比依赖于数字强制更好，
But with numbers, it's better instead of relying upon that numeric coercion,
使用大于零的值，如果你是这个意思的话。
use something like greater than zero, if that's what you mean.
它不仅可以保护你免受那些角落里的一些情况的影响，不是所有的，而是一些。
Not only does it protect you from some of those corner cases, not all but some.
它可以保护您不受某些角落情况的影响，但它也具有更多的语义。
It protects you from some of those corner cases but it is also more semantic.
因为您在这里说的是，在长度大于零的情况下继续循环，
Because you are saying here, keep looping while the length is greater than zero,
而不是保持循环，而长度是真实的。
instead of keep looping while the length is truthy.
那到底是什么意思？
What does that even mean?
所以不要仅仅为了拯救几个角色而聪明，
So don't be clever just to save a couple of characters,
在显性更具交际性的地方，要更明确地说明这一点。
be more explicit about it in the places where explicitness is more communicative.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：我们已经讨论了其中一些。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: We already covered some of this.
我在幻灯片上跳到了前面。
I jumped ahead in my slides.
但空字符串的布尔值为false。
But the Boolean of an empty string is false.
非空字符串的布尔值是真的，这肯定会是一个难题。
The Boolean of a non-empty string is true, and that's certainly gonna be a gotcha.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：好的，未定义和空的布尔测试，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Okay, the Boolean tests for undefined and null,
我们知道这两个都在名单上。
we know that both of those are on the list.
我喜欢将null和undefined视为不可区分的值。
I like to treat null and undefined as indistinguishable values.
只要有可能。
Wherever possible.
并不总是可能将它们视为不可区分的。
It's not always possible to treat them as indistinguishable.
但在可能的情况下，我喜欢这样做，并且
But where possible, I like to do so, and
凝聚力实际上对此非常有帮助。
cohesion actually is very helpful for that.
但是关于布尔，因为我们知道它们都很强大，如果测试表明
But with respect to Boolean since we know that they're both forcy, if the test that
我们问的是这个东西有没有设置好，我们经常这样做。
we're asking for is has this thing been set or not, which we do often.
这东西是被设置在物体上还是它仍然开始。
Is this thing been set on object or is it still onset.
好吧，对我来说，这是完全合理的
All right, for me, that's a perfectly reasonable
在放置布尔强制，我可以接受。
in placing Boolean coercion that I'm okay with.
我不喜欢强迫和
I don't like to impose the coerce and
空的应变虚假的，而不是空的应变真实的。
empty strain the false and not empty strain the true.
我不喜欢强迫数字为真或假，但是
I don't like to impose the coerce numbers to true or false but
我很高兴要么说没有，要么说没有定义，
I am perfectly happy with either saying it's no or undefined,
这意味着它是未说的，这是错误的，或者它被设置为类似对象的东西。
meaning it's unsaid, and that's falsely or it's been set to something like an object.
然后它是棘手的，我使用所有的地方。
And then it's tricky and I use that all the all over the place.
所以在我看来，我觉得还可以，
So in my particular opinion, I think it's okay,
当我们具体讨论时，使用隐式到布尔强制
to use the implicit to Boolean coercion when we're specifically talking about
未定义决策的对象或NULL。
either an object or null undefined that decision making.
但是数字和字符串，因为他们有这么多角落的情况，
But the numbers and the strings, since they have so many corner cases,
我不认为隐含的强制有其自身的份量。
I don't think that that implicit coercion carries its own weight.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：我不太想在这里详细说明你是如何
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: I'm less trying to be prescriptive here about exactly how you
应该这样做，更多的尝试让你像JavaScript一样思考。
should do it, and more trying to get you to think like JavaScript.
然后你自己决定我在哪里画这些线。
And make your own determinations for where do I draw these lines.